[
  {
    "timestamp": "11/3/2024 14:24:23",
    "name": "PINK",
    "color": "#FF6384",
    "navigation": {
      "question": "How confident did you feel navigating during the test?",
      "confidence": 3,
      "reason": "I stumbled upon the DIY that I was looking for. There were multiple locations that I thought it could be in.",
      "simplifiedReason": "I found it by accident and it feels like I shouldn't have found it there. (Lighting & Ceiling Fans Ideas & Projects Section)"
    },
    "cart": {
      "question": "How confident do you feel about what's in your cart?",
      "confidence": 4,
      "reason": "I feel fairly confident. The necessary products for my task was right there when I opened the page.",
      "simplifiedReason": "I feel fairly confident. The necessary products for my project seems like it would be there."
    },
    "instructions": {
      "question": "How useful did you find the instructions provided in How to Sync Your Lights?",
      "confidence": 5,
      "reason": "I feel that it is very useful instructions. I can follow through step by step once I download the necessary app and connect my lights easily.",
      "simplifiedReason": "I can follow through step by step once I download the necessary app and connect my lights easily."
    },
    "materials": {
      "question": "What materials did you add to your cart?",
      "materials": [
        "Amazon Echo",
        "12 in. Multi-Color Smart Wi-Fi LED 4X Beam Light Kit",
        "EcoSmart (40-Watt)"
      ]
    },
    "feedback": {
      "question": "What general feedback do you have?",
      "response": "The website is very confusing. It doesn't have a clear structure and it's hard to find the DIY that I'm looking for.",
      "simplifiedResponse": "<em>I would prefer a search bar. Not having that makes my life hard.</em>"
    },
    "useDIY": {
      "question": "Would you use the DIY section of Home Depot for your own applications/projects?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "reason": "I didn't know that Home depot had a DIY section before. Hopefully I can use it now when I have issues around my house that are too small to ask my landlord for help with.",
      "simplifiedReason": "I didn't know Home depot had this section. I would use it for small issues around my house."
    },
    "satisfaction": 4
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "11/3/2024 14:44:32",
    "name": "BLUE",
    "color": "#36A2EB",
    "navigation": {
      "question": "How confident did you feel navigating during the test?",
      "confidence": 4,
      "reason": "I knew it was somewhere and had to be reasonably organized so I just had to think of where they would categorize it",
      "simplifiedReason": "Well it had to be somewhere, so I just thought where they would categorize it."
    },
    "cart": {
      "question": "How confident do you feel about what's in your cart?",
      "confidence": 2,
      "reason": "The examples in the article were flat triangle lights, I'm sure it will work with the bulbs suggested but it's interesting that it's set up like that.",
      "simplifiedReason": "The images shown in the article were triangle lights, but the bulbs suggested were regular bulbs.<a style='text-decoration: none' href='#1'><sup>[1]</sup></a>"
    },
    "instructions": {
      "question": "How useful did you find the instructions provided in How to Sync Your Lights?",
      "confidence": 4,
      "reason": "It seemed like it's somewhat self explainitory once you download the app",
      "simplifiedReason": "It seemed like it's somewhat self explanatory once you download the app."
    },
    "materials": {
      "question": "What materials did you add to your cart?",
      "materials": [
        "Globe Electric",
        "EcoSmart (40-Watt)"
      ]
    },
    "feedback": {
      "question": "What general feedback do you have?",
      "response": "The groups/tabs are very general so it's hard to understand the organization and where your project would fit under.",
      "simplifiedResponse": "The categories are too generalized, so it's hard to know where your project will be."
    },
    "useDIY": {
      "question": "Would you use the DIY section of Home Depot for your own applications/projects?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "reason": "If I googled a DIY and home depot came up i would use their project but I would seek out the home depot website to do a DIY",
      "simplifiedReason": "<b>I would use the DIY section but I'd google for that specific page. Not search it through home depot.</b>"
    },
    "satisfaction": 4
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "11/6/2024 18:22:54",
    "name": "YELLOW",
    "color": "#FFCE56",
    "navigation": {
      "question": "How confident did you feel navigating during the test?",
      "confidence": 2,
      "reason": "I wasn't sure exactly what I was looking for",
      "simplifiedReason": "I didn't know what I was looking for."
    },
    "cart": {
      "question": "How confident do you feel about what's in your cart?",
      "confidence": 4,
      "reason": "It was a straightforward purchase",
      "simplifiedReason": "It's pretty straightforward"
    },
    "instructions": {
      "question": "How useful did you find the instructions provided in How to Sync Your Lights?",
      "confidence": 4,
      "reason": "It walked you through the process step by step",
      "simplifiedReason": "It walked you through the process step by step"
    },
    "materials": {
      "question": "What materials did you add to your cart?",
      "materials": [
        "Globe Electric"
      ]
    },
    "feedback": {
      "question": "What general feedback do you have?",
      "response": "Knowing that there was a specific section I was looking for and not just general information",
      "simplifiedResponse": "I would've liked to know there was a specific section I was looking for and not general information."
    },
    "useDIY": {
      "question": "Would you use the DIY section of Home Depot for your own applications/projects?",
      "answer": "No",
      "reason": "It would be much faster to do a google search or ask someone else for advice",
      "simplifiedReason": "Google searching is faster."
    },
    "satisfaction": 3
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "11/6/2024 18:43:51",
    "name": "TURQUOISE",
    "color": "#4BC0C0",
    "navigation": {
      "question": "How confident did you feel navigating during the test?",
      "confidence": 2,
      "reason": "It took me a long time to find the correct tutorial.",
      "simplifiedReason": "<b>It took too long</b>"
    },
    "cart": {
      "question": "How confident do you feel about what's in your cart?",
      "confidence": 4,
      "reason": "It seems what in my cart is relevant to the project.",
      "simplifiedReason": "It seems what in my cart is relevant to the project."
    },
    "instructions": {
      "question": "How useful did you find the instructions provided in How to Sync Your Lights?",
      "confidence": 4,
      "reason": "The instructions were pretty clear just by skimming.",
      "simplifiedReason": "The instructions were pretty clear just by skimming."
    },
    "materials": {
      "question": "What materials did you add to your cart?",
      "materials": [
        "EcoSmart (40-Watt)",
        "EcoSmart (100-Watt)"
      ]
    },
    "feedback": {
      "question": "What general feedback do you have?",
      "response": "It was frustrating not being able to find the correct project under the tabs the website is using."
    },
    "useDIY": {
      "question": "Would you use the DIY section of Home Depot for your own applications/projects?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "reason": "Once you can find the correct project it could be useful.",
      "simplifiedReason": "Once you can find the correct project it could be useful."
    },
    "satisfaction": 3
  },
  {
    "timestamp": "11/7/2024 20:57:29",
    "name": "PURPLE",
    "color": "#9966FF",
    "navigation": {
      "question": "How confident did you feel navigating during the test?",
      "confidence": 3,
      "reason": "There were a lot of places I felt that it could be after hitting the DIY button initially. There were a lot of projects to sift through as well.",
      "simplifiedReason": "It felt like the guide could be in a lot of places."
    },
    "cart": {
      "question": "How confident do you feel about what's in your cart?",
      "confidence": 5,
      "reason": "If I am looking to do the type of project in this scenerio, this DIY project from Home depot is exactly what I would be looking for.",
      "simplifiedReason": "This is exactly what I would be looking for."
    },
    "instructions": {
      "question": "How useful did you find the instructions provided in How to Sync Your Lights?",
      "confidence": 5,
      "reason": "The instruction are in depth.",
      "simplifiedReason": "The instruction are in depth."
    },
    "materials": {
      "question": "What materials did you add to your cart?",
      "materials": ["Globe Electric"]
    },
    "feedback": {
      "question": "What general feedback do you have?",
      "response": "Navigating to this page was not the most easy. I got confused between the \"How to Projects\" and the \"all DIY Projects"
    },
    "useDIY": {
      "question": "Would you use the DIY section of Home Depot for your own applications/projects?",
      "answer": "Yes",
      "reason": "I would use the DIY section if I was looking to renovate my house/room and wanted inspiration or if I had a specific thing I wanted like the lights in this example that I know is popular and would think they would have a section on.",
      "simplifiedReason": "I would use the DIY section if I wanted inspiration to renovate my house."
    },
    "satisfaction": 3
  }
]